Holy 'A' in Science Class - I made myself clone!
The Other Me is a tv movie, family, comedy film directed by Manny Coto.
When Will Browning is threatened with military summer school if he doesn't get better
grades, he decides to do a science project that will definitely get an A.
So he buys some Ocean Pups, unhatched sea creatures that will look spectacular, but he hasn't
bargained for the cloning agent that the unscrupulous manufacturers have put in the kit.
Next thing he knows there's another him.
Will Browning / Twoie, played by Andrew Lawrence.
Dad, played by Mark L. Taylor.
Mom, played by Lori Hallier.
Allana Browning, played by Alison Pill.
Chuckie, played by Brenden Jefferson.
Conrad, played by Joe Grifasi.
The Other Me is a 2000 American science fiction comedy film released as a Disney Channel Original Movie about a
teenager who accidentally clones himself as a genius and ends up using his clone to pass school.
The movie is the 23rd Disney Channel Original Movie and
is based on the book Me Two by Mary C.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, clone,
slacker, junior high school, school project.
The tone is lighthearted.